[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Indiana is the name of Indiana Jones pet cat.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the name of the elongated diamond cut with pointed ends.", "correct_answer": "Marquise", "incorrect_answers": ["Heart Shaped", "Oval", "Princess"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What did  Wilhelm Schickard invent?", "correct_answer": "the first automatic calculator", "incorrect_answers": ["the pneumatic drill", "celluloid", "the integrated circuit"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many red balls are in a game of snooker?", "correct_answer": "15", "incorrect_answers": ["3", "1", "8"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the Latin word  omnivore stand for?", "correct_answer": "Eating everything", "incorrect_answers": ["Fast eater", "Eating constantly", "Eating whatever"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A specimen from which of these species was listed in the Guinness Book of World Records as the longest bony fish alive?", "correct_answer": "Oarfish", "incorrect_answers": ["Whale shark", "Bluefin tuna", "Blue whale"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The inner layer of the turtles shell contains 60 bones-- including parts of the turtles ribs and backbone.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Oxytocin is an important hormone for the human body especially for women. What is it responsible for?", "correct_answer": "Contractions of the uterus", "incorrect_answers": ["Development of the uterus", "Development of the ovaries", "Ovulation"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many different types of wolves including sub-species are there around the world?", "correct_answer": "9", "incorrect_answers": ["Over 100", "44", "3"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the first childrens book to be number one on the New York Times Best Seller list?", "correct_answer": "Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire", "incorrect_answers": ["Madeline", "Green Eggs and Ham", "Goodnight Moon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Fungi take important part in which phase of the nutrient cycling and exchange?", "correct_answer": "Organic matter decomposition", "incorrect_answers": ["Organic matter formation", "Organic matter recomposition", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the creator of the \u201cPeanuts\u201d cartoon, that featured characters like Lucy, Linus, Snoopy and Charlie Brown?", "correct_answer": "Charles Schulz", "incorrect_answers": ["Charles Addams", "Dr. Suess", "Matt Groening"]}]